[
  {
    "question": "Pharmacology is the science that deals with the study of medicinal products in terms of:",
    "options": [
      "origin",
      "physical structure",
      "kinetics and their action",
      "toxicity"
    ],
    "answer": "kinetics and their action"
  },
  {
    "question": "The allopathic principle was introduced by:",
    "options": [
      "Euphrast",
      "Hahnemann",
      "Hippocrates",
      "Galenos",
      "Paracelsus"
    ],
    "answer": "Hahnemann"
  },
  {
    "question": "The principles of homeopathy are the:",
    "options": [
      "principle of complementarity",
      "principle of similarity",
      "principle of infinitesimal doses",
      "principle of individualised treatment",
      "principle of substituted dosage"
    ],
    "answer": "principle of similarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacognosy deals with:",
    "options": [
      "synthesis and chemical structure of the drugs, knowledge of drugs from which medicinal substances are extracted",
      "the main therapeutic characteristics",
      "the effect of drug on laboratory animals or isolated organs"
    ],
    "answer": "synthesis and chemical structure of the drugs, knowledge of drugs from which medicinal substances are extracted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Clinical pharmacodynamics aims the effect of medicines:",
    "options": [
      "during treatment",
      "on laboratory animals or isolated organs"
    ],
    "answer": "during treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacokinetics is the pharmacology branch that deals with the:",
    "options": [
      "study of drug circulation in organism",
      "temporal alterations- dose relation",
      "physico - chemical properties of drugs"
    ],
    "answer": "study of drug circulation in organism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacokinetics sub-branches are:",
    "options": [
      "invasion",
      "coupling",
      "evasion"
    ],
    "answer": "no answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invasion phase includes:",
    "options": [
      "drugs absorption",
      "drugs metabolism",
      "drugs distribution",
      "drugs disposal"
    ],
    "answer": "drugs absorption"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacometry studies the:",
    "options": [
      "effect of medicines during treatment",
      "movement of drug within the body",
      "measurements of drugs’ effect intensity"
    ],
    "answer": "measurements of drugs’ effect intensity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Therapeutic efficacy of drugs on affections is dealt by:",
    "options": [
      "pharmacodynamics",
      "pharmacokinetics",
      "clinical pharmacology",
      "pharmacometry"
    ],
    "answer": "clinical pharmacology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacogenetics deals with the:",
    "options": [
      "prescribing and preparing medicinal forms",
      "study of drugs chronic or acute toxicity",
      "correlation between: activity of intracellular biochemical substances and components"
    ],
    "answer": "correlation between: activity of intracellular biochemical substances and components"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pharmacogenetics deals with:",
    "options": [
      "the study of drugs chronic or acute toxicity",
      "the drug influence on genetic factors",
      "the correlations between the enzymatic activity and genome"
    ],
    "answer": "the correlations between the enzymatic activity and genome"
  },
  {
    "question": "Molecular pharmacology establishes correlations between:",
    "options": [
      "the activity of intracellular biochemical substances and components",
      "drug side effects",
      "synthesis and chemical structure of the active substances"
    ],
    "answer": "the activity of intracellular biochemical substances and components"
  },
  {
    "question": "Molecular pharmacology establishes correlations between:",
    "options": [
      "adverse effects of drugs",
      "synthesis and chemical structure of the active substances",
      "effect of medicines on humans and animals"
    ],
    "answer": "synthesis and chemical structure of the active substances"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bioavailability refers to:",
    "options": [
      "how the substance is released from the drug form",
      "elements which determine the absorption and diffusion of substances",
      "correlations established between the activity of biochemical substances and components"
    ],
    "answer": "elements which determine the absorption and diffusion of substances"
  },
  {
    "question": "Biopharmacy deals with:",
    "options": [
      "the release way of active substances",
      "relations between physico - chemical properties of active substances",
      "form preparation and drug administration",
      "pharmacokinetic parameters and their effects"
    ],
    "answer": "pharmacokinetic parameters and their effects"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first phase of dissolution of the tablets:",
    "options": [
      "disaggregating",
      "disintegration",
      "spraying"
    ],
    "answer": "disintegration"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first stage of dissolution of capsules is:",
    "options": [
      "disintegration",
      "disaggregation"
    ],
    "answer": "disintegration"
  },
  {
    "question": "A drug is:",
    "options": [
      "a substance of vegetable, animal or synthetic origin entering the body's metabolism and being strictly necessary",
      "a substance that introduced into the body produces general disorder"
    ],
    "answer": "a substance that introduced into the body produces general disorder"
  },
  {
    "question": "A drug is a substance:",
    "options": [
      "used in diagnosis, treatment, mitigation or prevention of a disease",
      "of vegetable, animal or synthetic origin entering the body's metabolism being necessary"
    ],
    "answer": "used in diagnosis, treatment, mitigation or prevention of a disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "A drug is able to:",
    "options": [
      "make it possible to recognize, remove, ease or prevent symptoms",
      "make it possible to recognize or influence organic structures, functions or behavior typology",
      "to be a plastic source and reserve with whom the body maintains its life"
    ],
    "answer": "make it possible to recognize, remove, ease or prevent symptoms"
  },
  {
    "question": "An ideal drug has:",
    "options": [
      "a precise activity",
      "a known mechanism of action",
      "constant efficiency"
    ],
    "answer": "a precise activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "An ideal drug has:",
    "options": [
      "constant efficiency",
      "tolerable side effects",
      "absence of side effects"
    ],
    "answer": "tolerable side effects"
  },
  {
    "question": "All drugs that are absorbed in the body are toxic:",
    "options": [
      "in higher doses than therapeutic",
      "below the therapeutic dose",
      "in therapeutic doses"
    ],
    "answer": "in higher doses than therapeutic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Food - medicine - toxic can be, for example:",
    "options": [
      "acetyl salicylic acid",
      "glucose",
      "minerals",
      "hormones"
    ],
    "answer": "acetyl salicylic acid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Food - medicine - toxic can be, for example:",
    "options": [
      "microelements",
      "minerals",
      "vitamins"
    ],
    "answer": "microelements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Standardization drug includes:",
    "options": [
      "adoption of tests that determine the purity and identity of a source of medicine",
      "recommendations related to dose size",
      "recommendations on the frequency of administration"
    ],
    "answer": "adoption of tests that determine the purity and identity of a source of medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Pharmacopoeia is given the:",
    "options": [
      "accepted name",
      "officinal name",
      "owner’s name"
    ],
    "answer": "officinal name"
  },
  {
    "question": "In current clinical practice is used the drug’s:",
    "options": [
      "Latin name",
      "official name",
      "trade name"
    ],
    "answer": "trade name"
  },
  {
    "question": "The drug’s Common International Name (DCI) is determined by:",
    "options": [
      "chemical structure",
      "product’s Latin name",
      "filed name of the active substance"
    ],
    "answer": "chemical structure"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first Pharmacopoeia appeared in:",
    "options": [
      "Japan",
      "China",
      "Sumer",
      "Greece"
    ],
    "answer": "Sumer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Romanian Pharmacopoeia appeared to date from:",
    "options": [
      "X - edition",
      "XI - edition",
      "XII - edition"
    ],
    "answer": "XI - edition"
  },
  {
    "question": "Medications can be given",
    "options": [
      "magisterially",
      "officinal",
      "typified",
      "standardized"
    ],
    "answer": "magisterially"
  },
  {
    "question": "The dosage form means:",
    "options": [
      "pharmacy executable form with a fixed composition",
      "finite presentation of a drug for administration"
    ],
    "answer": "finite presentation of a drug for administration"
  },
  {
    "question": "The chemical name is:",
    "options": [
      "officinal name in pharmacopoeia",
      "the correlation of the chemical structure",
      "producing company name given"
    ],
    "answer": "the correlation of the chemical structure"
  },
  {
    "question": "The bioavailability of a drug is the relationship of:",
    "options": [
      "peak plasma drug test and reference drug",
      "variability expressed as a percentage of a reference product compared with a product under test"
    ],
    "answer": "variability expressed as a percentage of a reference product compared with a product under test"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bioavailability of a drug is relationship of:",
    "options": [
      "variability expressed as a percentage of a reference medicinal product compared to a drug test",
      "blood test drug concentration compared to a reference medicinal",
      "peak plasma drug test and reference drug"
    ],
    "answer": "variability expressed as a percentage of a reference medicinal product compared to a drug test"
  },
  {
    "question": "The therapeutic effect of a drug is influenced primarily due to:",
    "options": [
      "dissolution constant",
      "absorption constant",
      "biological half-life",
      "rate of passage through lipophilic barriers",
      "elimination constant",
      "the constant accumulation in tissues"
    ],
    "answer": "absorption constant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bioavailability is:",
    "options": [
      "inversely proportional to the dissolution rate",
      "directly proportional to the rate of dissolution",
      "It is not affected by this parameter"
    ],
    "answer": "directly proportional to the rate of dissolution"
  },
  {
    "question": "An oral solution preparation form has a:",
    "options": [
      "great availability",
      "low availability",
      "equal to an bolus oral preparation"
    ],
    "answer": "great availability"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bioequivalence of a drug is determined by:",
    "options": [
      "its chemical bioequivalence",
      "its clinical bioequivalence",
      "its therapeutic bioequivalence",
      "isomeric bioequivalence",
      "all above"
    ],
    "answer": "all above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Polymorphism is the property of a drug:",
    "options": [
      "to determine different therapeutic effect at the same species",
      "to determine the clinical responses identical, but different speeds",
      "to determine different therapeutic effects depending on the species"
    ],
    "answer": "to determine different therapeutic effects depending on the species"
  },
  {
    "question": "Polymorphism is the property of a drug to:",
    "options": [
      "to determine different therapeutic effects at the same species",
      "crystallize different",
      "to determine the clinical responses identical, but different speeds"
    ],
    "answer": "crystallize different"
  },
  {
    "question": "Polymorphs of active substances have:",
    "options": [
      "totally different physical and chemical properties",
      "identical physical properties but different chemical properties",
      "different physical properties but chemical identical"
    ],
    "answer": "different physical properties but chemical identical"
  },
  {
    "question": "Polymorphs of active substances:",
    "options": [
      "identical physical but different chemical properties",
      "identical physico-chemical properties and different chemical",
      "chemical and physical properties totally different"
    ],
    "answer": "chemical and physical properties totally different"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thermodynamic unstable polymorphs are called also:",
    "options": [
      "hipostable",
      "metastable",
      "thermolysis"
    ],
    "answer": "metastable"
  },
  {
    "question": "The amorphous forms, as compared to the crystalline or anhydrous, have a dissolution speed usually:",
    "options": [
      "smaller",
      "greater",
      "equal"
    ],
    "answer": "greater"
  },
  {
    "question": "Designation of polymorphs is made with:",
    "options": [
      "Arabic numerals",
      "uppercase",
      "roman numerals"
    ],
    "answer": "roman numerals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aspirin given as monoparticles causes:",
    "options": [
      "far fewer gastric bleeding",
      "more stomach bleeding",
      "as many gastric bleeding as macroparticles"
    ],
    "answer": "far fewer gastric bleeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nitrofurantoin administered in the form of microcrystals (10μm), causes effect:",
    "options": [
      "more efficient",
      "dizziness and nosea",
      "effect identical to that produced by the larger crystal forms"
    ],
    "answer": "more efficient"
  },
  {
    "question": "Antihelmintic digestive products for a complex action, must:",
    "options": [
      "dissolve very rapidly",
      "dissolve slowly",
      "not dissolve, but stationed at the action site"
    ],
    "answer": "dissolve slowly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Griseofulvin shredded ultrafine allows healing skin mycoses using only half the usual recommended dose.",
    "options": [
      "real",
      "false",
      "action is not influenced by the particle size"
    ],
    "answer": "real"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cortisone with a great grinding will have action 20 times slower than the finely ground.",
    "options": [
      "action is not influenced",
      "false",
      "real"
    ],
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "question": "Barium sulfate fine particles are:",
    "options": [
      "a very good digestive",
      "a digestive irritant (because it forms granulomas)",
      "removed as such due to the reduction of particle"
    ],
    "answer": "a digestive irritant (because it forms granulomas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease size of hydroxypropiophenone crystals entails:",
    "options": [
      "two times faster inhibition of gonadotropins",
      "loss of specific inhibitory activity",
      "diversion of estrogenic activity"
    ],
    "answer": "two times faster inhibition of gonadotropins"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great reduction of the particle size generate:",
    "options": [
      "solubility decreasing",
      "rheological properties change",
      "environment moisture absorbing",
      "loss of stability"
    ],
    "answer": "rheological properties change"
  },
  {
    "question": "A deliquescent active substance is:",
    "options": [
      "a substance that has the ability to dispose water of crystallization",
      "an active substance that can lower the melting point of another active substance",
      "a substance that has the ability to absorb quantities of vapors to be transformed into its liquid form"
    ],
    "answer": "a substance that has the ability to absorb quantities of vapors to be transformed into its liquid form"
  },
  {
    "question": "A deliquescent active substance is:",
    "options": [
      "an active substance that can lower the melting point of another active substance",
      "a substance that has the ability to give up water of crystallization"
    ],
    "answer": "a substance that has the ability to give up water of crystallization"
  },
  {
    "question": "An efflorescent active substance is:",
    "options": [
      "a substance that can lower the melting point of the other active substances",
      "a substance which may lose all or part of crystallization water",
      "a hygroscopic substance capable of absorbing moisture from the air"
    ],
    "answer": "a substance which may lose all or part of crystallization water"
  },
  {
    "question": "An eutectic mixture is:",
    "options": [
      "a combination of active substances that decrease each others melting point and ultimately liquefaction",
      "a combination of substances that change their hygroscopicity",
      "an association that determines the loss of water of crystallization"
    ],
    "answer": "a combination of active substances that decrease each others melting point and ultimately liquefaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these substances is efflorescent?",
    "options": [
      "aluminum sulphate",
      "zinc carbonate",
      "borax",
      "aluminum silicate",
      "codeine sulfate"
    ],
    "answer": "aluminum sulphate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these combinations is not deliquescent but efflorescent?",
    "options": [
      "aluminium sulphate - borax",
      "phenol - thymol",
      "camphor - Menthol",
      "aspirin - acetanilide"
    ],
    "answer": "aluminium sulphate - borax"
  },
  {
    "question": "An oral tablet will dissolve in (after R.Ph X)",
    "options": [
      "15 minutes",
      "within 5 minutes",
      "30-60 minutes"
    ],
    "answer": "30-60 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "A solution is considered weak alkaline at a pH value between:",
    "options": [
      "7.5-10",
      "6.5 to 7.5",
      "10-12"
    ],
    "answer": "7.5-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "A euhidric pH is a:",
    "options": [
      "pH is adjusted towards acidic or alkaline",
      "pH adjusted to optimum stability",
      "pH adjusted to a total dissociation of solute"
    ],
    "answer": "pH adjusted to optimum stability"
  },
  {
    "question": "Liophobic colloids are:",
    "options": [
      "macromolecular compounds",
      "corpuscular compounds",
      "association colloids"
    ],
    "answer": "corpuscular compounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "Liofobic colloids are insoluble substances in dispersed phase being a set of neutral atoms or molecules that:",
    "options": [
      "have affinity for the dispersion medium",
      "have affinity for dispersion mode"
    ],
    "answer": "have affinity for dispersion mode"
  },
  {
    "question": "Plasma substitutes are administered iv because:",
    "options": [
      "have a high molecular weight",
      "do not cross the intestinal wall",
      "replace the red blood cell mass"
    ],
    "answer": "have a high molecular weight"
  },
  {
    "question": "Strictly i.v solutions can be administered with extreme pH:",
    "options": [
      "only acid",
      "only basic",
      "both acidic and basic conditions"
    ],
    "answer": "both acidic and basic conditions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Blood has an increased potential buffer than other tissues:",
    "options": [
      "real",
      "false",
      "blood has no buffer system"
    ],
    "answer": "real"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drug solutions with a lower molecular concentration than blood serum are called:",
    "options": [
      "hypotonic",
      "Isotonic",
      "hypertonic"
    ],
    "answer": "hypotonic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hypertonic dehydration is expressed through:",
    "options": [
      "increase cellular spaces and edema",
      "intake of electrolytes without input energy solutions",
      "loss of water without loss of electrolytes"
    ],
    "answer": "loss of water without loss of electrolytes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrolyte balance may be amended:",
    "options": [
      "changing acid-base balance",
      "glandular disorders and kidney",
      "inadequate sodium intake"
    ],
    "answer": "changing acid-base balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which explanation is correct for im injections",
    "options": [
      "hypotonic solutions IM causes turgor, swelling protoplasm, expansion of the cell membrane, even plasmolyzing",
      "the cell membrane voltage translates into pain",
      "excessive hypertonic solutions IM causes moisture, protoplasm expands"
    ],
    "answer": "the cell membrane voltage translates into pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which explanation is correct for im injections?",
    "options": [
      "hypertonic solutions IM dry the area, releasing cellular water",
      "protoplasm shrinks its volume and detaches from the membrane",
      "permeability alterations, with the final hemolysis"
    ],
    "answer": "hypertonic solutions IM dry the area, releasing cellular water"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which explanation is correct if IV injection?",
    "options": [
      "hypertonic solutions in excess affect the viability of cells (osmotic variation), the phenomenon of hemolysis can be faster",
      "a hypertonic solution should be administered only IV.",
      "in contact with hypotonic solutions erythrocytes swell and burst due to osmotic pressure",
      "Interstitial fluid circuit is slow and preferably not to use in this case"
    ],
    "answer": "hypertonic solutions in excess affect the viability of cells (osmotic variation), the phenomenon of hemolysis can be faster"
  },
  {
    "question": "Injections to be very well tolerated by the body must be blood serum:",
    "options": [
      "hypotonic",
      "isotonic",
      "hypertonic",
      "it has no importance"
    ],
    "answer": "isotonic"
  },
  {
    "question": "A drug solution will be isotonic with serum when:",
    "options": [
      "it has the same osmotic pressure",
      "the same freezing point",
      "it has the same molecular concentration"
    ],
    "answer": "it has the same osmotic pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hyperhydration isotonic entails:",
    "options": [
      "massive intake of water and / or energy solutions without electrolyte intake",
      "water depletion and accumulation of electrolytes",
      "increasing intercellular space and edema"
    ],
    "answer": "increasing intercellular space and edema"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pyrogenic substances are:",
    "options": [
      "natural substances, endotoxins from microorganisms",
      "thermoset macropolizaharide substances",
      "unsterile synthetic substances"
    ],
    "answer": "natural substances, endotoxins from microorganisms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pyrogens can produce:",
    "options": [
      "hypothalamic centers impairment (for 2-12 hours)",
      "a specific clinical picture: rapid pulse, respiratory changes, hyperthermia in 15-60 minutes",
      "hyperexcitation and hypothermia followed by exitus in 10-15 minutes"
    ],
    "answer": "a specific clinical picture: rapid pulse, respiratory changes, hyperthermia in 15-60 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "A preparation for infusion contains:",
    "options": [
      "drugs with pharmacodynamic activity",
      "dispersion in the form of suspensions",
      "molecular and colloidal dispersions, emulsions rarely"
    ],
    "answer": "molecular and colloidal dispersions, emulsions rarely"
  },
  {
    "question": "The rate of aerosol to the respiratory tract absorption compared to absorption by the iv route is:",
    "options": [
      "lower",
      "higher",
      "at least equal"
    ],
    "answer": "lower"
  },
  {
    "question": "The aerosols can be used to achieve systemic effects:",
    "options": [
      "yes",
      "no",
      "have only local effect"
    ],
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most appropriate size for spray medicine to be held in bronchioles is:",
    "options": [
      "20-30 µm",
      "0.8 - 2 µm",
      "10 - 20 µm",
      "2-5 µm"
    ],
    "answer": "2-5 µm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thixotropy is:",
    "options": [
      "the ability of a liquid to cover a wide surface area",
      "the ability of an ointment to cover a wide surface area",
      "the ability of an ointment to return, more or less to the original shape"
    ],
    "answer": "the ability of an ointment to return, more or less to the original shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Acanthosis test gives data on:",
    "options": [
      "tolerance to solutions with increasing dose administered IV",
      "the degree of swelling of the tissue after IM",
      "skin tolerance"
    ],
    "answer": "skin tolerance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intrarectaly can be given:",
    "options": [
      "sedative",
      "analgesics",
      "antispasmodics"
    ],
    "answer": "sedative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intrarectal way will not be chosen for:",
    "options": [
      "animals too young",
      "rectal mucosal lesions",
      "animals in fatigue"
    ],
    "answer": "rectal mucosal lesions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hepatic barrier has an essential role, being:",
    "options": [
      "an advantage in administering drugs",
      "a disadvantage in the administration",
      "an advantage in poisonings",
      "a disadvantage in intoxication"
    ],
    "answer": "an advantage in poisonings"
  },
  {
    "question": "An alkaline metal salt of penicillin generates diffusible ions as compared with an organic salt in:",
    "options": [
      "20-30 minutes with a duration of action is 4-6 hours",
      "6-hour ,duration of action of 18 hours"
    ],
    "answer": "20-30 minutes with a duration of action is 4-6 hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "Between i.m drug injection sites are bioavailability differences:",
    "options": [
      "true",
      "False",
      "is dependent on muscle group"
    ],
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "question": "After sc administration of ampicillin in the shoulders, peak plasma will occur in:",
    "options": [
      "3.9 hours",
      "3.3 hours",
      "4.6 hours"
    ],
    "answer": "3.3 hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "The tolerance to pain in animals, depending on the route of administration, increases:",
    "options": [
      "IV < IM < SC",
      "SC < IM < IV",
      "IM < SC < IV"
    ],
    "answer": "IV < IM < SC"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the basis of homeopathy were the first principles:",
    "options": [
      "isopathy",
      "zooiasic",
      "vedic"
    ],
    "answer": "isopathy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first book of veterinary homeopathy was published in 1837 in:",
    "options": [
      "Austria - Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "answer": "Austria - Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The benefits of homeopathy are:",
    "options": [
      "the use of very small doses",
      "efficacy in diseases where the body reactivity is blocked",
      "achieving rapid and uncomplicated results",
      "potency choice, even wrong, is not harmful"
    ],
    "answer": "the use of very small doses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Homeopathy has the drawback:",
    "options": [
      "is not effective in severe poisoning or cancer",
      "is not effective in the fields of harmful interference",
      "injections are painful and toxic in wrong choice potencies"
    ],
    "answer": "is not effective in severe poisoning or cancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hahnemiene principles of homeopathy are:",
    "options": [
      "principle of similarity",
      "the principle of antagonism",
      "the principle of dilution",
      "the principle of individualization"
    ],
    "answer": "principle of similarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "In homeopathy, healing occurs rapidly late or sometimes after a phase of worsening auspicious:",
    "options": [
      "no worsening of disease treatment is considered as auspicious",
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    "answer": "true"
  }
]
